The truth is out there… and it’s big!
Bigfoot Family is a animation, adventure, family
film directed by Jérémie Degruson.
Bigfoot, Adam's father, wants to use his fame for a good cause.
Protecting a large wildlife reserve in Alaska
sounds like the perfect opportunity!
When Bigfoot mysteriously disappears without a trace, Adam and his animal friends
will brave anything to find him again and save the nature reserve.
Adam (voice), played by Jules Medcraft.
Arlo (voice), played by David Lodge.
Connor Mandrake (voice), played by Grant George.
Emma (voice), played by Shyloh Oostwald.
Moose (voice) / Principle Jones (voice) / Wolf (voice), played by Joey Camen.
Guard 1 (voice), played by Kyle Hebert.
Bigfoot Family is a 2020 animated fantasy adventure comedy film directed by Ben
Stassen and Jeremy Degruson, and written by Bob Barlen and Cal Brunker.
An English-language Belgian-French co-production, it is the
sequel to the 2017 film The Son of Bigfoot.
In the film, Bigfoot has become famous after returning home
and uses his fame to fight an oil company.
When he disappears without a trace, it is up to Adam, his
mother, and their animal friends to rescue him.
It premiered at the 2020 Annecy International Animation Film Festival,
before releasing in France and Belgium on 5 August 2020.
The film explores themes of bigfoot, family, candid, adoring, amused.